Guide to the Shailer Mathews Papers 1892-1942
University of Chicago Library
- Shailer Mathews, Engagements, H-Q, 1921 (retained as sample) (Box 32, Folder 5)
- Shailer Mathews, Engagements, R-Z, 1921 (retained as sample) (Box 32, Folder 6)
- Chicago Church Federation, 1921 (Box 33, Folder 1)
- China Relief, 1921 (Box 33, Folder 2)
- Divinity School, University Preachers, 1921-1922 (Box 33, Folder 3)
- Shailer Mathews/Personal Correspondence, 1921-1922 (Box 33, Folder 4)
- Northern Baptist Convention/General Correspondence 1921-1922 (Box 33, Folder 5)
- Northern Baptist Convention, Board of Promotion, 1921-1922 (Box 33, Folder 6)
- Northern Baptist Convention, Investigation Committee, 1921-1922 (Box 34, Folder 1)
- Federal Council of the Churches of Christ in America/League to Enforce Peace, and the Church Peace Union, January, 1921-January, 1923 (Box 34, Folder 2)
- Federal Council of the Churches of Christ in America/League to Enforce Peace, and the Church Peace Union, January, 1921-January, 1923 (Box 34, Folder 3)
- Federal Council of the Churches of Christ in America/League to Enforce Peace, and the Church Peace Union, January, 1921-January, 1923 (Box 34, Folder 4)
- Baptist Theological Union, 1921-1924 (Box 34, Folder 5)
- Divinity School/General Correspondence A-B, 1922 (Box 35, Folder 1)
- Divinity School/General Correspondence C-K, 1922 (Box 35, Folder 2)
- Divinity School/General Correspondence L-R, 1922 (Box 35, Folder 3)
- Divinity School/General Correspondence S-Z, 1922 (Box 35, Folder 4)
- Divinity School, Curriculum, 1922 (Box 35, Folder 5)
- M, H. P. Judson correspondence, 1922 (Box 35, Folder 6)
- Divinity School, President's Report, 1922-1923 (Box 36, Folder 1)
- Divinity School, University Preachers, 1922-1923 (Box 36, Folder 2)
- Shailer Mathews/Chautaugua Institute, 1922-1923 (Box 36, Folder 3)
- Shailer Mathews/Chautaugua Institute, 1922-1923 (Box 36, Folder 4)
- Shailer Mathews/Chautaugua Institute, 1922-1923 (Box 36, Folder 5)
- Shailer Mathews, Fundamentalism, 1922-1924 (Box 36, Folder 6)
- Shailer Mathews, Macmillan Company, 1922-1924 (retained as sample) (Box 37, Folder 1)
- Divinity School/General Correspondence A, 1923 (Box 37, Folder 2)
- Divinity School/General Correspondence B, 1923 (Box 37, Folder 3)
- Divinity School/General Correspondence C, 1923 (Box 37, Folder 4)
- Divinity School/General Correspondence D-J, 1923 (Box 37, Folder 5)
- Divinity School/General Correspondence K-R, 1923 (Box 38, Folder 1)
- Divinity School/General Correspondence S-Z, 1923 (Box 38, Folder 2)
- Divinity School, Publications of the faculty, 1923 (Box 38, Folder 3)
- Shailer Mathews/Chautaugua Institute, 1923 (Box 38, Folder 4)
- Shailer Mathews, Engagements, A-G, 1923 (retained as sample) (Box 38, Folder 5)
- Shailer Mathews, Engagements, H-O, 1923 (retained as sample) (Box 38, Folder 6)
- Shailer Mathews, Engagements, Personal Correspondence-Z, 1923 (retained as sample) (Box 38, Folder 7)
- Shailer Mathews/Personal Correspondence, Reviews and articles, 1923 (Box 39, Folder 1)
- Divinity School, College of Missions, 1923 (Box 39, Folder 2)
- Divinity School, President's Report, 1923-1924 (Box 39, Folder 3)
- Divinity School, Apartments, 1923-1924 (retained as sample) (Box 39, Folder 4)
- Divinity School, University Preachers, 1923-1924 (Box 39, Folder 5)
- Shailer Mathews, Speaking engagements, A-L, 1923-1924 (retained as sample) (Box 39, Folder 6)
- Shailer Mathews, Speaking engagements, M-Z, 1923-1924 (retained as sample) (Box 39, Folder 7)
- Shailer Mathews, D. Ameton and Company, 1923-1924 (Box 40, Folder 1)
- Shailer Mathews/C, 1923-1924 (Box 40, Folder 2)
- Shailer Mathews/C, 1923-1924 (Box 40, Folder 3)
- Shailer Mathews/Personal Correspondence, 1923-1924 (Box 40, Folder 4)
- Divinity School/General Correspondence A-B, 1924 (Box 40, Folder 5)
- Divinity School/General Correspondence C, 1924 (Box 40, Folder 6)
- Divinity School/General Correspondence D-J, 1924 (Box 41, Folder 1)
- Divinity School/General Correspondence K-M, 1924 (Box 41, Folder 2)
- Divinity School/General Correspondence N-Q, 1924 (Box 41, Folder 3)
- Divinity School/General Correspondence R-Z, 1924 (Box 41, Folder 4)
- Divinity School, President's Report, 1924-1925 (Box 41, Folder 5)
- Divinity School, University Preachers, 1924-1925 (Box 41, Folder 6)
- Baptist Theological Union, Board of Trustees, Minutes, 1925-1928 (Box 42, Folder 1)
- Baptist Theological Union, Board of Trustees, Minutes, 1929-1934 (Box 42, Folder 2)
- Century of Progress Exposition, 1933 (Box 42, Folder 3)
- Divinity School, Pastors' Institute, 1934 (summary of lectures) (Box 42, Folder 4)
- Divinity School, Pastors' Institute, 1937 (Box 42, Folder 5)
- Theological Faculties Union, to 1938 (memorials, appreciations, etc.) (Box 42, Folder 6)
- Divinity School, Pastors' Institute, 1938 (Box 42, Folder 7)
- Divinity School, Pastors' Institute, 1939 (Box 43, Folder 1)
- Divinity School, Pastors' Institute, 1940 (Box 43, Folder 2)
- Divinity School, Dr. Olof Hedeen, 1940-1941 (Box 43, Folder 3)
- Divinity School, Divinity School News, January, 1941 (Box 43, Folder 4)
- Divinity School, Pastors' Institute, 1941 (Box 43, Folder 5)
- Shailer Mathews?, Fragments of a travel "Journal," 1941 (Box 43, Folder 6)
- Divinity School, Pastors' Institute, 1942 (Box 43, Folder 7)
- Publications from the "Universal Christian Conference on Life and Work Conferences," 1925-1928 (Box 44, Folder 1)
- Publications from the "Universal Christian Conference on Life and Work Conference," 1925 (Box 44, Folder 2)
- Hymn book, 1925 (Box 44, Folder 3)
- Life and Work: Daily Bulletin of Universal Christian Conference at Stockholm, Aug 19-21, Aug 24-28, 1925 (Box 44, Folder 4)
- Materials from Universal Christian Conference on Life and Work Conference;" invitations, membership cared, order of procession, program (Box 44, Folder 5)
- Photographs and postcards taken at "Universal Christian Conference on Life and Work Conference," 1925 (Box 44, Folder 6)
- Photograph, King and Queen of Sweden, 1925 (Box 44, Folder 7)
- Broadside advertisement, "William Tyndale's Translation of the New Testament" (Box 44, Folder 8)